qbusinesssolution.com 2010-01-02

# Q BUSINESS SOLUTION

PRIVACY POLICY

Q Business Solution ****takes the security of your personal information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will not rent, sell or share your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers with any unaffiliated third parties.

This Privacy Policy applies to all services that are hosted on Q Business Solution ****website, whether Q Business Solution ****(or its subsidiaries or one of its affiliates) offers the services. By accepting the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Q Business Solution ****Terms of Service.

 **Notification of Changes**

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Q Business Solution ****service or as we incorporate suggestions from our customers. If we are going to use or disclose your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time we collected the information, you will have a choice as to whether or not we use or disclose your information in this new manner. Any material changes will be effective only after we notify you via e-mail with at least 30 days’ notice of the amended Privacy Policy.

We will post the amended Privacy Policy prominently on our website so that you can always review what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check the Q Business Solution ****website at QBusinessSolution ****.com at any time for the most current version of our Privacy Policy.

Advertisers and affiliates on the Q Business Solution ****website may include links to third party websites. Q Business Solution ****is not responsible for their operations, including but not limited to their information practices. Their privacy statements govern those sites. Users submitting information to or through these third party websites should review the privacy statement of these sites before providing them with personally identifiable information.

 **Required Information**

To open a Q Business Solution ****account, you must provide your name, company name (if any), valid address, scanned copy of a valid Driver’s License or Passport, date of birth, phone number and e-mail address. This required information may be necessary for us to process transactions, issue a new password if you forget or lose your password, protect you against third party fraud and to contact you should the need arise in administering your account. Never give out your login or password to any third parties.

If you choose to register or apply for certain optional features or products offered through the Q Business Solution ****websites, you will be required to provide additional information to establish that you qualify for such features or products.

 **Web Information**

Because of the way that Internet communication standards work, when you arrive at or leave the Q Business Solution ****website, we automatically receive the Internet address of the site that you came from or are going to. We also collect information on which pages of our website you visit while you are on the Q Business Solution ****site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our website. We may collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We do not track the websites that you visit before or after you leave the Q Business Solution ****site.

 **“Cookies”**

“Cookies” are small files of data that reside on your computer and allow us to recognize you as a Q Business Solution ****member if you return to the site using the same computer and browser. We send a “session cookie” to your computer if and when you log in to your Q Business Solution ****account by entering your login and password. These cookies allow us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session, so that you don’t need to re-enter your password multiple times. Once you log out or close your browser, these session cookies expire and no longer have any effect. We may share cookie information regarding whether or not a certain user is already registered with Q Business Solution ****with certain merchants with whom we have an official co-marketing relationship.

 **Customer Service Communication**

If you send us correspondence, we may retain such information in our records of your account. We may also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence from Q Business Solution ****to you. We may retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of our Terms of Service. We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law.

From time to time, we may offer optional questionnaires and surveys to our members for such purposes as collecting demographic information or assessing members’ interests and needs. The use of the information collected will be explained in detail in the survey itself. If we collect personally identifiable information from our members in these questionnaires and surveys, the members will be given notice of how the information will be used prior to their participation in the survey or questionnaire.

 **Internal Uses**

We collect, store and process your personal information on servers. We use the information we collect about you in order to provide our services and process your transactions, to provide customer service, to determine your eligibility to receive offers for special features or products, and to improve our products and services. We give access to individually identifiable information about our users only to those employees who require it to fulfill customer service requests.

Q Business Solution ****will NOT sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information to third parties. Q Business Solution ****will not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties except in the limited circumstances described below. These third parties are limited by law or by contract from using the information for secondary purposes beyond the purposes for which the information is shared. We disclose the information we collect to affiliates that perform marketing services on our behalf

We disclose information that we in good faith believe is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our Terms of Service. Specifically, this means that if we conduct a fraud investigation and conclude that one side has engaged in deceptive practices, we can give that person or entity’s contact information (but not account information) to victims who request it.

We disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from private parties in a civil action.

We disclose information to your agent or legal representative (such as the holder of a power of attorney that you grant, or a guardian appointed for you).

We share your information with our parent, subsidiaries and joint ventures to help coordinate the services we provide to you, enforce our terms and conditions, and promote trust and safety.

 **Our Contacts**

We communicate with members on a regular basis via e-mail to provide requested services to resolve customer complaints or investigate suspicious transactions. We use your e-mail address to confirm your opening of a Q Business Solution ****account, to send you notice of payments that you send or receive through Q Business Solution ****to send information about important changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures required by law.

 **IP Information**

We use IP addresses, browser types and access times to analyze trends, administer the site, improve site performance and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Q Business Solution ****does not tolerate unsolicited commercial e-mail or “spam.” Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you may not add a Q Business Solution ****affiliate to your mail list (e-mail or physical mail) without their express consent after adequate disclosure. Our anti-spam policy is strictly enforced.

 **Information Security**

Q Business Solution ****handles your member information with high standards of information security. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.

The security of your Q Business Solution ****account also relies on your protection of your Q Business Solution ****login and password. You should not share your Q Business Solution ****login or password with anyone. Q Business Solution ****representatives will never ask you for your password, so any e-mail or other communication requesting your password should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious. If you do share your Q Business Solution ****password with a third party for any reason, including third party promises of providing you additional services such as account aggregation, the third party will have access to your account and your personal information, and you may be responsible for actions taken using your password. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your account and changing your user settings. Contact us right away.
